<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Homepage on AIM RSF September Event Series</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/</link><description>Recent content in Homepage on AIM RSF September Event Series</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 15:14:39 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Test Page</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/events/test/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/events/test/</guid><description>&lt;!doctype html> My First Heading My first paragraph.</description></item><item><title>September Seminar</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/events/seminar-series/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/events/seminar-series/</guid><description>Meag Doherty of National Institute of Health&amp;rsquo;s All of Us research program presents &amp;ldquo;Everyone has a Say: Embedding human-centred design (HCD) in the research setting&amp;rdquo; and discusses how elements of Human-Centred Design and its frameworks have been used by the National Institute of Health&amp;rsquo;s All of Us research program to “build one of the most diverse health databases in history&amp;quot;.
Tuesday 13th September, 13:30 - 14:30
Introduction The AIM RSF Seminars are a regular series of open invitation talks from leading voices in data science, AI, healthcare and those with lived experience dealing with multiple long-term conditions (MLTC).</description></item><item><title>Collaboration Cafe</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/events/collab-cafe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/events/collab-cafe/</guid><description>AIM RSF Collaboration Cafes are drop in co-working sessions focused on collaboration and community building. Sessions are open to anyone working on AIM projects and occur on the third Thursday of every month.
Next session: Thursday 15th September, 14:00 - 16:00
Sessions are hosted on Zoom; If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have a calendar invite and would like to attend, please contact the Community Manager for Open Collaboration, Eirini Zormpa at ezormpa@turing.</description></item><item><title>Discussion Panel</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/events/panel-discussion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/events/panel-discussion/</guid><description>Professor Ronan Lyons (SAIL), Lynsey Cross (HDR-UK), and Meag Doherty (NIH-AoU) discuss PPIE best practices, and provide insight from their experiences leading PPIE efforts at a National level.
Friday 16th September, 10:00 - 11:00
Public Involvement for Better Research The genuine inclusion of individuals from diverse backgrounds is both an ethical imperative and vital for scientific validity. Failing to reach and involve affected people, or distorting or diminishing their input, makes research less comprehensive and nuanced while representative research, incorporating a rich range of perspectives, improves scientific validity, and delivers broader and more equitable impact.</description></item><item><title>Cross-Consortia Session</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/events/cross-consortia-session/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/events/cross-consortia-session/</guid><description>Cross-Consortia Sessions are open to all members of the AIM Consortia and RSF affiliates. In this session, AutSPACEs research team will present on the methods of public engagement, co-design, and inclusive research that have led to the success of an entirely co-created research project.
Monday 26th September, 10:00 - 11:00
The session will be hosted on Zoom, please contact the AIM RSF Community Manager at sbatchelor@turing.ac.uk for joining details.
Citizen Science and Co-creation About AutSPACEs AutSPACEs is a community-led citizen science project seeking to make environments more accessible for autistic people.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/contact/</guid><description>Lorem markdownum aequalis strigis. Saetigeri iubeas, vultu huic alvum nondum de obside ut laniavit arbor palmis, cum quin. Rupes vetat videndo, armigerae crimen habet Priamum nec.</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/events/contact-us/</guid><description>The Research Support Facility (RSF), based at The Alan Turing Institute with collaborators from Swansea University and the University of Edinburgh, offers AI and advanced data science support to the research teams part of the NIHR's Artificial Intelligence for Multiple Long-Term Conditions (AIM) project, and acts as a hub to foster collaboration across the AIM consortia.
For more information about the RSF, please visit our webpage (AI formultiple long-term conditions: Research Support Facility | The AlanTuring Institute) or contact us direct at: aimrsf@turing.</description></item></channel></rss>